[

  {
    "question": "Which HTTP method is used to create a resource in REST_________",
    "answer": "POST"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which HTTP method is used for partial update in REST _________",
    "answer": "PATCH"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which HTTP method is used for complete object update in REST _________",
    "answer": "PUT"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which HTTP method is used for retrieve the resource in REST _________",
    "answer": "GET"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which HTTP method is used for delete the resource in REST _________",
    "answer": "DELETE"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which annotation binds JSON data to a Java object______________",
    "answer": "@RequestBody"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which annotation activates the validations ______________",
    "answer": "@Valid"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which annotation is used to make the REST controller class______________",
    "answer": "@RestController"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which annotation is used to make the service class______________",
    "answer": "@Service"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which annotation is used to make the repository______________",
    "answer": "@Repository"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which annotation is used to allow cross-origin requests ___________",
    "answer": "@CrossOrigin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which annotation inside ControllerAdvice handles exceptions _____________",
    "answer": "@ExceptionHandler"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which annotation is used to specify the primary key in an entity class _____",
    "answer": "@Id"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the annotation to change the table name _______",
    "answer": "@Table"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the annotation to change the column name _______",
    "answer": "@Column"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which annotation automatically generates the primary key value ________",
    "answer": "@GeneratedValue"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the annotation used to take the base URL for all endpoints _________",
    "answer": "@RequestMapping"
  },
  {
    "question": "@Controller + @ResponseBody = __________",
    "answer": "@RestController"
  },
  {
    "question": "What HTTP status code represents Not Found _______",
    "answer": "404"
  },
  {
    "question": "What HTTP status code represents OK _______",
    "answer": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "What HTTP status code represents Created _____",
    "answer": "201"
  },
  {
    "question": "What HTTP status code represents deleted No content _____",
    "answer": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "What HTTP status code represents BAD requested data _____",
    "answer": "400"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the default port of Tomcat ________",
    "answer": "8080"
  },
  {
    "question": "REST APIs help decouple frontend and backend (true/false) ________",
    "answer": "true"
  }
]
